wotol.com 2003-08-11

# Wotol

|    
|   
---  
|  |  |  |   

**Grippers**  
An exclusive promotion on Wotol for rappier looms.  

>  **Check the offers**  

---  
|  |  |  |   
  
Textile, Garment, Home furnishing, Machinery, Others:  
• Products for sale   
• Products wanted   
• [ **Post your classified**](mailto:contact@wotol.com?subject=This%20is%20my%20classified)   
  
---  
|  |  |  |   

**Next auction**  
**Very large** auction. three factories the same day! One **air jet weaving** factory and two **printing and finisshing** factories.   
Venue: Lyon - France  
15 May 2003  

>  **For more info**  
  
---  
|  |  |  |   
  
Consult or post your tenders 

>  **Click here**  

| 

  **Privacy Statement**

**Personal information**  
Protecting the individual's privacy on the Internet is crucial to the future of Internet-based business and the move toward a true Internet economy. In general, you can visit Wotol on the Web without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. There are times, however, when we may need information from you, such as your name and address. It is our intent to let you know before we collect personal information from you on the Internet.   
If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need -- to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. If you tell us that you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will respect your wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends and statistics, and then we discard it.   
Wotol has created this privacy statement to demonstrate its firm commitment to secure and trustworthy Internet commerce and the individual's privacy. 

Home | Textile and Garment | Machinery | Software and measurement  
Register your company | Modify your company profile | Commercial services   
  
First Visit? | [Design & Trends](mailto:contact@wotol.com) | Useful Links | [Advertising](mailto:contact@wotol.com?subject=Advertising) | Disclaimer | Corporate information  
Privacy Statement | Copyright WOTOL 2000 \- All rights reserved - [Contact](mailto:contact@wotol.com) |  |  |   
---  
|  |   
  
Get better audience with our online showroom.   
  
|    **View the Demo**  
  **Check our offer**   
|   
  **Please visit**  
|  **YUEN TAÏ**  
**Total solution provider for textile printing**  
  **Visit the Showroom**   
|   
  **and also**  
|  **LOGIC ART**  
**Total color management provider for dyeing house**  
Dosing, dispensing, measurement, monitoring, planning...   
  **Visit the Showroom**   
|   
|  |   
---  
|  |   
| **All you can find and do on WOTOL** |   
|  |   
| Receive latest news about World Textile On Line  
**Enter Email address** |   
|   
**Signup** |   
|  |   
| It's FREE and gives you  
an international audience  
**Register now** |   
|  |   
|   • Exhibitions  
 • Conferences and Seminars  
 • Promote your Events  |   
|  |   
|  For more info, click here |
